Guide to the Stanford Student Letters and Memoirs Collection SC0103
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford student letters and memoirs collection
1871-2016
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Dyke, Charles Bartlett.
Stanford University. Libraries. Department of Special Collections and University Archives
SC0103
9 Linear Feet (27 boxes)
109.62 gigabyte(s)
Scope and Contents
The first series of this collection contains letters, reminiscences, diaries and account books, autobiographies, and other items from a number of Stanford University students. Most of the letters are written home to family members; typical subjects include academic affairs, social life on campus and off, fraternity and sorority affairs, and athletics. Other subjects include events at the Stanford home and the settlement of Leland Stanford's estate.
The second series consists of email and text messages sent home from students.
Access to Collection
The materials are open for research use.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged in two series. Series 1: letters, series 2: emails and text messages.
Existence and Location of Copies
The materials have been digitized and are available online: https://searchworks.stanford.edu/view/4085089.
Beckwith, Burnham P. (Burnham Putman); Marschutz, Herbert Stanton.; Nichols, Walter E.; Nolan, Lloyd.; Osborne, Clarence.; Hyde, Harriet Sophia.; Kautz, Austin.; Klette, Ernest.; Barzen, Alva Emrich.; Allen, Tex Bollman.; Allabach, Lucy; Crawford, Irma Zschokke.; Dyke, Charles Bartlett.; Colliver, John.; Burr, Myron.; Blake, Thomas B.; Durand, Samuel B.; Dyke, Charles Bartlett.; Perry, Frederick Jewell.; Stanford University -- General subdivision--Students.;; Schulte, William.; Sindo, Michitaro.; Stahl, Edith Osborne; Evans-Wentz, W. Y. (Walter Yeeling); Taggert, James D.; Taggert, Katherine.; Payne, Theodora.; Stanford University. Libraries. Department of Special Collections and University Archives; Osborne, Raymond.; Osborne, Henry.; Payne, Rose.; Osborne, Sherill.
- Letters and memoirs, Series 1
  - Harriet Sophia (Hallie) Hyde Letters, 1894-1895
    Custodial History note
    Gift of William Hyde Irwin, 1973
    Scope and Contents note
    Letters, 1894 to 1895, from Harriet Sophia (Hallie) Hyde, a freshman at Stanford, to her mother, Mrs. William Birelie Hyde, including one letter mentioning the campus reaction to news of the decision on the settlement of Leland Stanford's estate.
    - Correspondence fom Harriet (Hallie) Hyde to her mother, Fall 1894 -Spring 1895; 10 items (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Thomas A. Blake Diary, 1907
    Purchased from Edward Morrill and Son, 1973
    This bound typescript entitled "A Semester at Stanford" includes contemporary photographs and a note from Blake to Mrs. A. G. Everett, describing the manuscript. Subjects include hazing, the Frosh-Soph Tie-Up, the Plug Ugly fights, excursions off campus, pajama parades, and the football game between Stanford and Berkeley.
    - "A semester at Stanford," [1907], bound together with contemporary photographs, 124 pages (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Blake to Mrs. A. G. Everett; and unbound photographs, Dec. 1908 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - John Colliver Letters and Memorabilia, 1894-1895
    Gift of Mrs. Nancy Bohlander, 1976
    This series consists of four letters from J. T. Colliver to his son John Adams Colliver (A.B. 1896) at Stanford, along with a handwritten fight song and miscellaneous receipts.
    - Colliver, John, 1894-1895 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Ernest Klette Letters, 1904
    Gift of Mrs. Harold Hjelm, November 1975
    Ernest Klette attended Stanford University from 1902 to 1905; this series consists of two letters and one postcard from Klette to his sister Birdie discussing a reception for new students at Mrs. Stanford's house, the choir, and his schoolwork.
    - Klette, Ernest, Aug. -Nov. 1904 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Osborne Family letters, 1871-1914; Series 2
    April 2002: These letters have been removed and processed with additional letters as Osborne Family Papers (SC0636)
  - James D. Taggart and Katherine Taggart Spinks Papers, 1905-1915
    Gift of Mr. Taggart Spinks, 1975
    Miscellaneous receipts, cancelled checks, and student documents of James Dean Taggart, class of 1909, and Katherine Taggart Spinks, class of 1914.
    Taggart, James Deacon.; Spinks, Kathrine Taggart.
    - Taggart, miscelleous documents, 1905-1915 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Frederic Jewell Perry Letters, 1896-1900
    Gift of Mrs. Ruth G. Allen, 1976
    This series contains approximately 125 letters from Frederic Jewell Perry, class of 1900, to his mother, discussing student life on campus, especially the affairs of the Kappa Sigma fraternity.
    - Letters, 1896 -1898 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Letters, 1899 -1900 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - William Henry Schulte Letter, 1893
    - Schulte, William Henry (A.B. May 1895) to his sister Nannie, discussing professors and literary activities., 1893 Nov. 5 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Tex Bollman Allen Papers, 1929-1930
    This collection of papers from Tex Bollman Allen, class of 1933, includes his letters to his family discussing his friends, sports, classes, and potential fraternity life; one letter from Benjamin A. Clark, 3 Dec. 1929; and miscellaneous receipts and notes.
    - Receipts, notes, and letter from B. A. Clark (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Letters to Allen family, Jan. 1930 -May 1930 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Herbert Stanton Marshutz Letter, 1941
    - Letter to Kenneth Smith, Stanford Alumni Association, regarding the Stanford Crew Team of 1912 to 1918, 1941 Dec. 24 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Austin Kautz Letter, 1892
    - Letter to Bessie Anderson regarding the December 1892 Big Game, 1892 Dec. 17; Transcript included (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Lloyd Nolan Letter
    - Letter to Dave, (possibly David Lamson), relating to Nolan's blossoming stage career, 17 April (1935?) (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Payne Family Letters, 1895-1897
    These letters were written by Rose Payne, A.B. 1898, and Theodora Payne, A.B. 1900, to "Nannie" in San Jose, possibly an aunt. They describe their student life at Stanford including classes and lectures, athletics, sorority matters, and social events with other students and faculty. There is also some mention of Jane Stanford and the govenment suit against the estate of Leland Stanford.
    - Correspondence, 1895 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      - Freshman-Sophomore reception; death of Mrs. Pease., 1895 October 6
      - Production of "Tribly;" Bonfire; celebration on account of decision for suit processions., 1895 October 13
      - Sorority question-refusal of Kappa bids., 1895 October 18
      - Roble reception for the faculty., 1895 October 28
      - Big Game; Thanksgiving Day at Stanford., 1895 November 10
      - Big Game results; Thanksgiving vacation and dance; course descriptions., undated
      - Cheating incident; possible appointment of student committee on cheating; burning of the chemical lab; Prof. Anderson's article on "Napoleon's Retreat from Moscow.", 1895 December 17
    - Correspondence, 1896 (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - Prof. Clarke description; Fort Stoniax bank failure., 1896 Feb.
      - Celebrations over suit decision; Founder's Day; University committees., 1896 March 15
      - Vacation dances; Prof. Anderson's course., 1896 March 24
      - Chancy M. Deperd speech with Cornelius Vanderbilt., 1896 March 4
      - House mortgage; junior dance., 1896 April 20
      - Exams and commencement; Roble reception for the faculty., 1896 May 4
      - French Revolution lectures; English 11; Stanford Day., 1896 May
      - Commencement week., 1896 May 29
      - Description of courses., 1896 Sept. 4
      - McKinley's election; Dr. Jordan's party; Thanksgiving Dance., 1896 November 8
      - Visit with Mrs. Stanford; description of her home and dress and personality., 1896 Nov. 14
      - Card party at the home of Dr. and Mrs. Angell with Dr. and Mrs. Fairclough., 1896 Nov.
      - Winning of Big Game; pride in the University; Thanksgiving.
      - Thanksgiving Dance; Mrs. Stanford's contribution., 1896 Nov. 29
      - Prof. Hudson's course re Mathew Arnold., 1896 Dec. 11
    - Correspondence, 1897 (Box 2, Folder 24)
      - Suspension of 7 Roble girls and Mrs. Clement (Roble director) due to drinking incident; mentions Mrs. Baker as replacement., 1897 Jan. 1
      - Dr. Jordan's 46th birthday party; visit with Prof. Anderson and his family., 1897 Jan. 23
      - Jordan's poem published in Sequoia; dance with Sigma Rho Eta., 1897 Feb. 6
      - Invitation to Sophomore Cotilion., 1897 Feb. 16
      - Description of Cotilion; comments on fraternity question at Stanford., 1897 Feb
      - Informal party at the home of Prof. Allardice with Profs. Campbell, Kellogg, Fairclough and Hodges; proposed improvment of Roble dining room., 1897 March 2
      - New Orleans French Grand Opera Co. at the California and description of Shakespeare exam., 1897 March 15
      - Welsh rarebit party given by Mr. Nash in Encina; comments on the party, Mr. Nash.
      - Intercollegiate field day and debate., 1897 April 25
      - Change in room and board., 1897 May 2
      - Jordan's reception for the seniors; mentions Mrs. Stanford., 1897 May 31
      - Description of classes., 1897 Oct. 4
  - Lucy Allabach Correpondence, 1891-1895
    - Transcripts of Allabach's letters to family, primarily her mother, 1891-1895 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Edward Meylan Memoirs, 1979
    Gift of Edward F. Meylan, 1979
    - Typescript memoirs of his student life stressing influence of particular professors, 1924-1927 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Myron Burr Correspondence, 1905-1940
    This series includes letters by Myron Burr, class of 1907, written while a student, describing Jane Stanford's funeral and the 1906 earthquake; and correspondence pertaining to reunions of the Class of 1907, 1932-1940.
    - Correspondence, 1905-1906 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1932-1940 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Irma Zschokke Crawford Diary, 1968
    - Diary describing life in early Palo Alto, impressions of Jane Stanford, and experiences in the 1906 earthquake at Stanford., 1886-1968; Photocopy of typescript. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Samuel B. Durand Correspondence, 1893-1894
    Gift of Samuel R. Durand, 1981 and 1982
    Samuel B. Durand earned his Civil Engineering degree in May 1894; these letters to his brother discuss campus buildings, Benjamin Harrison's lecture series, Junior Day activities, Berkeley Day activities, student tennis matches, and his negative impression of David Starr Jordan, the University President.
    - Letters to his brother, 1893-1894 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Charles Bartlett Dyke Papers, 1893-1896
    Gift of P. Meissner, 1979
    - Diary of a journey from Ohio to California; and cash accounts at Stanford University, 1893; 1894-1896 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - W. Y. Evans-Wentz Papers, 1906-1927
    - Letters of recommendation from David Starr Jordan, Orrin Leslie Elliott, and J. E. McDowell; and letter from Evans-Wentz to Ray Lyman Wilbur regarding an educational trust fund, endowing a professorship at Stanford. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Student notes, unidentified
    - List of rules for student conduct, undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Burnham P. Beckwith Papers, 1923-1924, 1982
    Gift of Burnham P. Beckwith, January 1983
    These papers of Beckwith, class of 1926, include letters, a class paper, and a chapter from his autobiography. Subjects in the letters include his academic work, being on the staff of the student newspaper, excursions to San Francisco, his activities on the debating team, athletic and social events, and lectures attended, with occassional discussion of ideas such as socialism and religion.
    - Letters home to his parents, 1923 Jan. -Nov. (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Letters home to his parents; paper on religion; and two photographs: Beckwith with friends and Branner Hall, 1924 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - "My four years at Stanford, 1922-1926." Chapter VI, Autobiography of Burnham Putnam Beckwith, circa 1982 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Walter E. Nichols Letters, 1898-1899
    Gift of Mrs. Winifred Gabrielson, April 1984
    - Letters, Six letters to his cousin, Mabel, Sept. 1898-April 1899. (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Henrietta Martin Letters, 1893-1986
    - Two letters from Ellen F. Thompson; three letters from Dora Murdy, 4 Jan. 1893 and 30 Oct. 1893; 24 Dec. 1895, 12 Jan. 1895, and 26 March 1896 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Ethel C. Duncan Letter, 1906
    Gift of Mrs. Ralph Weinrichter, 1992
    - Letter to Andrew Durham, describing what she likes about Stanford, the fraternities, the surrounding countryside, and the students., 19 Jan. 1906 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Alva Emrich Barzen Letters, 1913
    Purchased from Howard Hein, 1985
    - Two letters to his family describing his race at a track event, writing for the student newspaper, fraternity life and affairs, and meetings with Charles Lathrop, business manager for the University, and John C. Branner, President of the University. (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - James Cone Letter, 1900 Oct. 6
    Gift of Mrs. Dorothy Cone Moore, 1985
    - Letter to his mother concerning football, boarding costs and the members of his club, and family matters. (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Michitaro Sindo Letters, 1901-1902
    Biographical/Historical note
    Michitaro Sindo, a Japanese student at Stanford from 1900 to 1906, worked with David S. Jordan on ichthyological studies and the Commission to study Hawaiian fishes. While at Stanford he was tutored by Elizabeth Cone, who earned her A.B. in English in 1901 and was a graduate student and assistant in the English Department, 1906-1908.
    These letters to Cone discuss his ichthyological work in Hawaii with Dr. Jordan, 1901, and in Samoa with Jordan and Dr. Kellogg, 1902; his description of Samoa and its people, including his visit to Robert Louis Stevenson's residence and grave; his assessment of Japanese home and social life (in reaction to an article in Outlook); and his academic work at Stanford, 1901.
    - Letters to Elizabeth Cone, 1901-1902 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Carl Emil Knecht Letters, 1895-1896
    Gift of Peter and Carl Knecht, 1985
    Knecht earned his B.A. in geology at Stanford in 1899 and his M.A. in 1900. After a year in California as a geologist, Knecht worked for several mining companies in South Africa. He died in Johannesburg on July 12, 1925.
    These letters were written to his family in Los Angeles from September 1895 to May 1896 and discuss his classes, exams, fees and expenses, the celebration on campus after decision in court case on Leland Stanford's estate, excursions to S. F. Bay, and advice from Dr. Branner. Also included is the English entrance exam test he took.
    - Letters, and English exam, 1895 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Letters, 1896 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Eri Horner Richardson Letters, 1905-1906
    Gift of Eri Horner Richarson, Jr., 1985
    Richardson attended classes at Stanford between 1905 and 1907. From evidence in the letters, he supported himself in part by rebuilding the Jordans' chimney after the 1906 earthquake.
    - Letter from G. A. Clark; sheet on self-support for students; and letter from Jessie Knight Jordan, with endorsement by D. S. Jordan on Richardson's work, 1905; 1905; 1906 Oct (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Beulah Weeks Letter, March 5, 1896
    Gift of Mrs. Beulah Weeks Hemenway, 1951
    - Letter to family regarding celebrations on campus after decision in court case on Leland Stanford's estate and an excursions into Santa Cruz mountains in the snow (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Joseph B. Scudder Letter, Nov. 26, 1924
    Gift of Tom Flood, 2007
    Scudder earned his A.B. in pre-law, June 1927.
    - Letter to his parents discussing Big Game and upcoming appearance in Rose Bowl against Notre Dame and his activities on Thanksgiving Day (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Leon Thomas David Letter, July 6, 1921
    Gift of Carolyn David Eskra, 2007
    David earned his A.B. in pre-law in June 1924 and his J.D. in 1926.
    - Letter to his parents relating the "paddling" he experienced as an Encina freshmen by upper classmen as well as the dunking tradition (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - George A. Tarbell Letters, 1902-1903
    Acquisition Information
    Gift of Mrs. Robert Jaffee, 1988.
    Biographical / Historical
    Tarbell earned his A.B. in electrical engineering in May 1907.
    - Three letters to his family generally about life on campus and his classes, including an encounter with Prof. Marx. (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Kurt Widmer minute letter, January 1930
    Gift of George Schaetti, 2010.
    - Pre-printed “Stanford University Minute Letter” postcard sent to Grete Hoffman [Romer], Jan 21, 1930 (Box 3, Folder 24)
      Scope and Contents
      The postcard has 6 segments with various options that the sender can check.
  - Mary Carol Stearns letters, 1946; Accession ARCH-2015-160
    - 1946-09-23 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - 1946-09-24 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - 1946-09-26 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - 1946-09-29 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - 1946-09-29 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Additional Mary Carol Stearns letters, Accession ARCH-2017-275
    - Letters, 1943-1946 (Box 1)
  - George D. Green letters, 1960 Jan-Jun; Accession ARCH-2016-028
    Letters from George to then girlfriend (now wife) Anne Rose Green from Stanford in Germany IV; copies typed of letters to parents.
    Overseas Studies
  - Bartlett/Gould family letters and diaries, 1906-1934; Accession ARCH-2016-034
    - Mabel Bartlett letters, circa 1906-1909 (Box 1)
    - Richard Bartlett Gould letters and diary, 1930-1934 (Box 1)
  - Katherine J. Stephenson letters, Accession ARCH-2016-035
    - Letters from Italy, 2015 (Box 1, Folders 1-4)
  - Hall family letters, 1916; Accession ARCH-2016-036
    - Letter from Benjamin Frederick Hall to Mrs. Addie S. C. Hall, 1916-4-23 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Letter from Myron Crawford Hall to Benjamin Frederick Hall, 1916-5-14 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - John Murray Huneke and Chrissie Kremer student letters, 1947-1983; ARCH-2016-050
    - John Murray Huneke letters home, 1947-1983
    - Chrissie Kremer letters home from Vienna and Cliveden, 1983
    - Photographs
  - Chris Seaman letter, 1973; ARCH-2016-059
    - Letter from Chris Seaman to Diane, Ned, Kate, and Anne Keller, 1973 (Box 1)
  - Elaine Lindheim (Class of 1963) letters, 1960-1963; ARCH-2016-071
    PDF scans of letters sent home from Elaine Lindheim (class of 1963).
  - Barbara Armentrout (Class of 1967) letters, 1965 Apr-Aug; ARCH-2016-072
    PDF scans of letters sent home from Stanford in France X by Barbara Armentrout (class of 1967).
  - Mary Caballero (Class of 2018) letters, ARCH-2016-073
    PDF scans of letters sent home from Mary Caballero (class of 2018).
  - Ethan Meyers (Class of 2014) letters, 2013-2015; ARCH-2016-076
    JPG images of letters sent home from Ethan Myers (class of 2014) on Mother's Day 2013 & 2015.
  - William Quinn (Class of 1992) letters home, 1991-1992; ARCH-2016-077
    PDF scans of letters sent home from William Quinn (Class of 1992).
  - Marijean Crow (Class of 1979) letters, ARCH-2015-129
    - Letters, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Letters, 1976-1979 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Eric Johnson (Class of 1991) letter, 1990; ARCH-2015-129
    - Letter, 1990 May 10 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Nancy Christine Smith letters, 1946-1947; ARCH-2016-081
    - Letters, 1946-1947 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Robert Lowell Swetzer (Class of 1951) letters, ARCH-2016-085
    - Letters, 1947-1952 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Vickie Rozell (Class of 1981) letters, ARCH-2016-086
  - Wendell Birkhofer (Class of 1978) letters, ARCH-2016-087
  - William R. Poppino (Class of 1956) letters, ARCH-2016-088
  - Julia Hamilton Conkling (Class of 1915, 1916 MA) letters, ARCH-2016-089
    - Letters, 1911-1913 (Box 1)
    - Letters, 1913-1915 (Box 2)
    - Letters, 1915-1916 (Box 3)
    - Photographs and memorabilia (Box 3)
  - Blossom Parke McBrier (Class of 1945) letter home, Accession ARCH-2016-123
    - Letter, 1943 (Box 1)
  - Fred Brosio (Class of 1957), letters, 1953; Accession ARCH-2017-041
  - Christina Kohlmann (Class of 2015), letters, 2016; Accession ARCH-2017-042
  - Lanny Levin (Class of 1971), letters, 1968, Accession ARCH-2017-043
  - Madeleine Rowell (Class of 2018), letters, 2015; Accession ARCH-2017-045
  - Russell Smith (Class of 1941), letters, 1938; Accession ARCH-2016-141
    - Photograph (Box 1)
  - Terry Yoschak Koehler (Class of 1966), letters, 1962-1966; Accession ARCH-2017-047
  - Theer, Maryeda Hayes (Class of 1957, MA 1958), letters, 1953-1956; Accession ARCH-2017-055
  - Peter King (Class of 1965), letters, 1961-1965; Accession ARCH-2017-056
  - Joseph L. Jacobs (Class of 1965) letters home, 1961-2015; Accession ARCH-2016-080
  - Alison Carpenter Davis (Class of 1975) letters, 1975-1977; Accession ARCH-2018-047
  - Mary Lesnett Carpenter (Class of 1948) letters, 1944-1948; Accession ARCH-2018-046
  - Anne Battle (Class of 1975) letters, Accession ARCH-2018-080
    - Letters, 1972-1973 (Box 1)
  - Will Prichard (Class of 1898) letter, 1894; Accession ARCH-2017-311
    - Letter, 1894 (Box 1)
  - Eleanor Elizabeth Hardman Furst Roberts (Class of 1933) letters, Accession ARCH-2018-094
    - Letters, 1931-1934 (Box 1)
  - Natalie Stevenson Rittenhouse (Class of 1948) letters, Accession ARCH-2018-096
    - Letters, 1945-1953 (Box 1-2)
- Emails and text messages, Series 2
  Email and text message correspondence between Stanford students and their families. Materials submitted to the University Archives electronically as part of the Stanford Alumni Legacy Project initiative. Emails are submitted directly to the Stanford University Archives at yourstanfordlegacy@stanford.edu; text messages are submitted directly to (415) 952-7241. Files consist of email and/or text messages, or screenshots thereof. Contextual explanations and descriptions of messages are sometimes provided by donors. File formats primarily include: .eml, .jpg, .pdf, .docx, .csv, and .htm.
  - Anonymous (Class of 2016), 2015; anon_001
  - Bennett-Fite, Nicole (Class of 2016), 2013-2015
  - Bruzek, Laine (Class of 2016), texts, 2013; Accession ARCH-ARCH-2017-048
  - Clonts, Michael (Class of 1985), 1982-1983
  - Franich, Darren (Class of 2007), 2006
  - Glazer, Grant (Class of 2017), 2013
  - Goetze,Catherine (Class of 2018), texts, 2016; Accession ARCH-2017-049
  - Hua, Vanessa (Class of 1997), 1995; ARCH-2016-074
  - Johnson, Bryant (Class of 2017), 2015
  - Larson, Sydney (MBA Class of 2015), ARCH-2016-075
  - Lucas, Christopher (Class of 2018), 2015
  - Morgan, Tamandra (Class of 2007), email, Accession ARCH-2017-051
  - Ram, Vignesh (MA, 2012) email, 2011; Accession ARCH-2017-094
  - Richardson, Kady (Class of 2018), texts, 2015; Accession ARCH-2017-052
  - Rosellini, Ben, undated
  - Rosen, Valerie (Class of 2013), 2009-2011
  - Rumberg, Roneil (Class of 2015), 2011
  - Seter, Jason (Class of 2018), texts, 2014; Accession ARCH-2017-053
  - Sharpe (Class of 2015)
  - Tjossem, Nora (Class of 2015), 2011; ARCH-2016-078
  - Toews, Erica (Class of 2010), email, 2008-2009; Accession ARCH-2017-054
  - Weber, David (Class of 2018), 2014
  - Weintz Cerf, Beppie (Class of 1979), 1976-03-29
    Weintz Cerf, Beppie; Weintz, J. Fred, Junior